Tissue Culture Association records
Tissue Culture Association records
- Series VII. Meetings, 1946-1986; bulk 1947-1980; 6200 items (9.75 linear feet)
  - Subseries VII.C. Decennial Review Conference, 1956–1976; 1,900 items (2.75 linear feet)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Session 3 Papers 1976 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Session 4 Papers 1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Session 5 Papers 1976 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Session 6 Papers 1976 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Session 8 Papers 1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Session 9 Papers 1976 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Session 10 Papers 1976 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Sessions 1-10 Discussions 1976 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Decennial Review Conference/Sessions Lecture Ledger 1976 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Decennial Review Conference/1ST Planning Meeting of Executive Board for 1976 (Oct.10,1974) (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ 2nd Planning Meeting of Executive Board for 1976 (Oct.17,1974) (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ 3rd Planning Meeting of Executive Board for 1976 (Oct.25,1974) (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Decennial Review Conference/4th Planning Meeting of Executive Board for 1976 (Nov.8,1974) (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Decennial Review Conference/5th Planning Meeting of Executive Board for 1976 (Dec.4,1974) (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Decennial Review Conference/7th Planning Meeting of Executive Board for 1976 (Jan.21,1975) (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Decennial Review Conference/7th Planning Meeting of Executive Board for 1976 (Jan.21,1975) (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Decennial Review Conference/7th Planning Meeting of Executive Board for 1976 (Jan. 21, 1975) (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Decennial Review Conference/8th Planning Meeting of Executive Board for 1976 (Apr. 2, 1975) (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Decennial Review Conference/9th Planning Meeting of Executive Board for 1976 (Apr. 29, 1975) (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Decennial Review Conference/11th Planning Meeting of Executive Board for 1976 (May 21, 1975) (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Decennial Review Conference/12th Planning Meeting of Executive Board for 1976 (Mar.19-20,1976) (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ 1976 Meeting/Ledger Sheets/Income Recap (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ 1976 Meeting/Ledger Sheets/Income Recap (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ 1976 Meeting/Ledger Sheets/Record of Checks Deposited and Disbursed (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ 1976 Meeting/Miscellaneous Ledgers (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ 1976 Meeting/Computer Print Out/Accounting 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Decennial Review Conference/ 1976 Meeting/Computer Print Out/Accounting 2 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Subseries VII.D. Miscellaneous Conferences and Audiotapes, 1946–1967; 50 items (.5 linear feet)
    - Conference on Tissue Culture 1946 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Conference on Tissue Culture Technique in Pharmocology (NY Academy of Sciences) 1954 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - International Tissue Culture Meeting 1957 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Michigan Academy of Science Meeting 1958 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Conference on The Use of Animal Cell Tissue and Organ Cultures in Radiology 1961 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Seventh Canadian Cancer Research Conference 1966 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - 9 Magnetic Reel to Reel Original Audio Tapes of the Conference on Cell Cultures for Virus Vaccine Production 1967 (Box 26)
- Series VIII. Publications, 1950-1986; bulk 1960-1979; 2400 items (3.5 linear feet)
  The series contains correspondence, reports, minutes, forms manuscripts, questionnaires, and printed matter. They are arranged into three sub-series: Bibliography & Index, Bulletins, Manual, Newsletter, and Miscellaneous Publications, and In Vitro. Each sub-series is arranged alphabetically by subject and then in date order.
  - Subseries VIII.A. Bibliography & Index, 1950-1977; 200 items (.25 linear feet)
    Correspondence, reports, and printed materials arranged alphabetically by subject and then in date order.
    - Bibliography/Correspondence/General 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Bibliography/General 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Bibliography/General 1972 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Bibliography/October House 1965-1968 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Bibliography/October House 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Bibliography/October House 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Bibliography/ Printed Bibliographies 1953, 1960-1963, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Bibliography/ Reports 1950, 1952, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Bibliography/ Reports 1968-1972 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Index of Tissue Culture/ Correspondence 1965-1970 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Index of Tissue Culture/ Correspondence 1972-1977 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Subseries VIII.B. Bulletins, Manual, Newsletter, and Miscellaneous Publications, 1947-1984; 600 items (.75 linear feet)
    Correspondence, forms, manuscripts, questionnaire arranged in alphabetical order by subject and title, printed materials arranged in date order.
    - Bulletins/1947-1950 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Bulletins/1951-1954 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Bulletins/1955-1958 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Bulletins/1959-1962 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Bulletins/1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Bulletins/1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Manual/Correspondence (Evans) 1975/5-1980/7 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Manual/Forms (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Manual/History, Format, Executive Board meeting Minutes concerning Manual 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Manual/Manuscript/Ball, F. et. al.- An Economical Roller Bottle (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Manual/Manuscript/Bryant, Jay – Earle’s Balanced Salt Solution (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Manual/Manuscript/Freeman, A.E. – Tissue Culture Mathematics (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Manual/Manuscript/Klein, Antley – Fundemental Cytosentrics Lab Procedures and Techniques (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Manual/Manuscript/Orr, M. – Tissue Culture Methods Manual (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Manual/Manuscript/Toji, Lorraine – Starch Gel Electrophoresis (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Manual/Manuscript/Winters, W.D., Neri, A. – Cultivation of Tissue and Cell Culture (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Manual/Questionnaire 1-100 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Manual/Questionnaire 101-200 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Manual/Questionnaire 201-300 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Manual/Questionnaire 301-400 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Manual/Questionnaire 401-500 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Manual/Questionnaire 501-600 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Manual/Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous/Cell Biology Proposal for Media Development Program (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous/Cell Databook (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous/Cryodeuer Newsletter 1968 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous/Explants 1965-68 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous/Newstrent 1970 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous/The NMRI Quarterly Review 1976 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous/TCA Report 1980 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous/TCA Report 1981 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous/TCA Report 1983 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous/TCA Report 1984 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous/Tissue Culture Section Department of HEW 1956,1960 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Newsletter/Correspondence and Memos 1968-1971 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Newsletter/Correspondence and Reports 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Newsletter/Correspondence and Reports 1974 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Newsletter/Correspondence 1975 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Newsletter/Correspondence and Reports 1976 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Newsletter/Correspondence and Reports 1977 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Newsletter/ 1968 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Newsletter/ 1969 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Newsletter/ 1970 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Newsletter/ 1971 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Newsletter/ 1972 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Newsletter/ 1973 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Newsletter/ 1974 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Newsletter/ 1975 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Newsletter/ 1976 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Newsletter/ 1977 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Subseries VIII.C. In Vitro, 1966-1978; 1,600 items (2.5 linear feet)
    Files containing articles, correspondence, reports, ledgers, page proofs, and copies of the journal are arranged in alphabetical order by type of document and then in date order. Articles are sub-divided by author and files arranged in alphabetical order by subject.
    - In Vitro/Accounting Code Number Index (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - In Vitro/ Advertising (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - In Vitro/ Article/ Chou, Janice et al (Synthesis of Alpha Subunit…) (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - In Vitro/ Article/Chou, Janice et al/ Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - In Vitro/ Article/Chou, Janice et al/ Photographs (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - In Vitro/ Article/Chou, Janice et al/ Review (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - In Vitro/ Article/Chou, Janice et al/ Revised Copy 1976/1 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - In Vitro/ Article/Chou, Janice et al/ Revised Original 1976/1 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - In Vitro/Article/Chen, T.R./Correspondence and Review (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - In Vitro/Article/Chen, T.R./Revised Copy 1975/2 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - In Vitro/Article/Duncan, G.R./Correspondence and Review 1978 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - In Vitro/Article/Kahn and Duncan/Page Proofs (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - In Vitro/Article/Langenbaugh, R. and Tompa/Plates (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - In Vitro/Article/Langenbaugh, R. and Tompa/Copy, Correspondence and Review (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - In Vitro/ Article/Langenbaugh, R. and Tompa/ Revised Original (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - In Vitro/Article/Mizrahi, A./Copy, Correspondence and Review (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - In Vitro/Article/Murashige, T. and Tisserat/Correspondence and Review (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - In Vitro/ Article/Murashige/Revised Original (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - In Vitro/ Audit Report 1977 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - In Vitro/ Budget 1970 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - In Vitro/ Copyright (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - In Vitro/ Correspondence 1966-1967/1 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - In Vitro/ Correspondence 1970 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - In Vitro/ Correspondence (Executive Board) 1971 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - In Vitro/ Correspondence (Evans) 1966-1975 (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - In Vitro/ Correspondence (Kahn) 1971 (Box 28, Folder 52)
    - In Vitro/ Correspondence (Miscellaneous and Notes) 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 53)
    - In Vitro/ Forms (Box 28, Folder 54)
    - In Vitro/ Issue Sales (Box 28, Folder 55)
    - In Vitro/ Journals Recieved (Box 28, Folder 56)
    - In Vitro/ Ledgers (Subscriptions)/1971-1974 (5) (Box 28, Folder 57)
    - In Vitro/ Ledgers (Subscriptions)/1971-1974 (4) (Box 28, Folder 58)
    - In Vitro/ Ledgers (Receipts)/1970-1974 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - In Vitro/ Ledgers (Subscriptions)/1970-1974 (1) (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - In Vitro/ Ledgers (Subscriptions)/1971-1974 (2) (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - In Vitro/ Ledgers (Subscriptions)/1971-1974 (3) (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - In Vitro/ Ledger Pages/Miscellaneous 1970-1978 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - In Vitro/ Ledger Pages/Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - In Vitro/Mono Sales 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - In Vitro/Page Charges 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - In Vitro/Page Proofs 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - In Vitro/ Publications List (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - In Vitro/ Reprint Sales (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - In Vitro/Subscription Expenditures (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - In Vitro/ TCA Meeting 1978 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - In Vitro/ TCA Sales (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Series IX. W. Alton Jones Cell Science Center (WAJCSC)
  Unprocessed.